Why would I lie to you?
هل تظن أنني أكذب عليك؟
Miss Chen is indeed pregnant.
الآنسة تشن حامل بالفعل.
The meal is ready.
الطعام جاهز.
Shall I bring it to you now?
هل أحضره لك الآن؟
Please let me know if you need anything.
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء، فلا تتردد في طلبه.
Why are you following me?
لماذا تتبعني؟
Aren't you his adjutant?
ألست مساعده؟
To protect your safety at all times.
لحمايتك عن قرب.
I almost forgot.
يبدو أنني كدت أنسى.
I can't just swing on a whim.
لا يمكنني التأرجح كما أشاء.
Didn't your governor say
ألم يقل القائد العام الخاص بكم
that he could fulfill all my wishes?
إنه سيلبي كل رغباتي؟
As long as Miss Chen orders,
كل ما تأمر به الآنسة تشن.
Then go prepare a car now.
إذن اذهب الآن وجهز سيارة.
Now that I'm pregnant with Fang Yanyun's child,
أنا الآن حامل بطفل فانغ يان يون.
since the governor won't let me leave,
بما أن القائد العام لا يسمح لي بالمغادرة
I'll give birth here at the governor's mansion.
سأنجب الطفل في مقر القائد العام.
Let Chen Qingyan stay in the Governor's mansion.
دع تشن تشينغ يان تبقى في مقر الحاكم العسكري.
Actually, I'm quite envious of you.
في الواقع، أنا أحسدك حقًا.
She can still make you worry so much.
لا يزال بإمكانها أن تجعلك قلقًا.
That's why they say you're capable of great things.
دعنا نقول إنك لا تزال قادرًا على إنجاز أشياء عظيمة.
You're being cuckolded and happily becoming a father.
أنت نفسك تعرضت للخيانة وأصبحت أبًا.
Now everyone in the mansion knows about it.
جعلت الجميع في المقر يعرفون.
This bastard child staying in the Governor's mansion.
هذا الابن غير الشرعي يبقى في مقر الحاكم العسكري.
Either get rid of the child,
إما أن تتخلص من الطفل.
or leave with her.
أو تغادر معها.
There's no other choice.
ليس هناك خيار آخر.
It will be like a natural miscarriage.
سيكون مثل الإجهاض الطبيعي.
Put the pears into the pot.
ضع الكمثرى في القدر.
Haven't you added a bit too much?
ألم تضف الكثير؟
I thought you had died in battle.
ظننت أنك قد استشهدت في المعركة.
So you're that eager for me to die?
هل تتمنى موتي هكذا؟
You lock me up here and then avoid me.
لقد حبستني هنا وأنت تتجنبني.
As long as you're willing to stay.
إذا وافقت على البقاء فقط.
Everyone in the mansion knows.
الجميع في المنزل يعرفون.
This is not your child.
هذا ليس طفلك.
General, don't you even care about your own
هل فقد القائد حتى
reputation anymore?
أدنى قدر من كرامته؟
My affairs are none of their business.
شؤوني ليست من اختصاصهم.
The general specifically instructed,
لقد أوصى القائد العسكري خصيصًا.
you must have proper meals three times a day.
يجب أن تتناول وجباتك الثلاث بشكل صحيح كل يوم.
even if you can't eat,
حتى لو لم تستطع تناول الطعام،
you should think of the child.
عليك أن تفكر في الطفل.
This is made with wild ginseng from Yunshui Mountain.
هذا مصنوع من الجينسنغ البري من جبال يونشوي،
I heard the general personally led people to collect it.
سمعت أن القائد العسكري أحضر أشخاصًا خصيصًا لجمعه.
I'm at their mercy.
الناس هم السكين والطاولة، وأنا السمكة.
Your blood is indeed cold.
دمك بارد حقًا كما توقعت.
Why don't you have some snacks instead?
أو يمكنك تناول بعض الحلوى.
As long as you're willing to stay,
طالما أنك على استعداد للبقاء.
Dr. Chen's morning sickness is so severe.
الدكتور تشن يعاني من غثيان الحمل بشكل شديد.
Are you really not hungry?
هل أنت حقا فاقد للشهية؟
You should try to understand Leng Sinian.
يجب أن تتفهمي لينغ سي نيان أيضا.
He's already fallen out with the Lin family for your sake.
لقد تشاجر مع عائلة لين من أجلك.
Now you're pregnant with someone else's child.
والآن أنت حامل بطفل شخص آخر.
It's difficult to explain to the Shuai family.
من الصعب تفسير الأمر لعائلة شواي.
He doesn't want the position of military governor.
إنه لا يريد منصب القائد العسكري.
If he intended to let you go,
إذا كان ينوي تركك ترحلين،
you wouldn't have drunk the soup with musk in it.
فلن تشربي الحساء المعطر بالمسك.
The gentle breeze caresses.
النسيم الخفيف يداعب.
The gentle breeze softly stirs your heart.
النسيم الخفيف يداعب قلبك برقة.
The gentle breeze softly stirs thoughts of you in my heart.
النسيم الخفيف يداعب قلبك الذي يشتاق إليك برقة.
The gentle breeze softly caresses.
النسيم الخفيف يداعب برقة.
The lake water reflects me clearly.
مياه البحيرة تنعكس علي.
Falling leaves cover the ground, as if you're gently here.
أوراق الشجر المتساقطة تغطي الأرض كأنها همسك الخفيف.
The rustling of falling leaves seems like your soft whisper.
أوراق الشجر المتساقطة تحفيف كأنها تسمع همسك الخفيف.
How many times have the flowers bloomed?
كم مرة تفتحت الزهور.
How many times have the flowers bloomed? The rain falls silently.
كم مرة تفتحت الزهور، والمطر يسقط بصمت.
Together, yet in vain.
نعتمد على بعضنا البعض، لكن القلب خائب.
Looking at you, longing to be together, all in vain.
أنظر إليك، أتمنى أن نعتمد على بعضنا البعض، لكن القلب خائب.
Looking at you, shaping our togetherness, all in vain.
أنظر إليك، أشكل اعتمادنا على بعضنا البعض، لكن القلب خائب.
Looking, if it's you, longing to be together.
أنظر، إذا كنت أنت، أتمنى أن نعتمد على بعضنا البعض.
Yet unable to resist, the heart's law.
لكن لا أقاوم، القلب يتبع القانون.
Yet unable to resist, the heart's obsession.
لكن لا أستطيع مقاومة، القلب مفتون.
If persistent, if following the heart, if desired.
إذا أصررت، إذا اتبعت قلبك، إذا كان ما.
If insistent,
إذا أصررت.
following the heart, if desired.
اتبع قلبك، إذا كان ما تريد.
If insistent, if following the heart, if desired.
إذا أصررت، إذا اتبعت قلبك، إذا كان ما تريد.
Delusional to occupy tender moments.
أوهام احتلال الأوقات الدافئة.
The night sways like your silhouette.
ظلال الليل تتمايل مثل ظلك.
Walking alone under the moon, memories surge.
المشي وحيدا تحت ضوء القمر يثير الذكريات.
In dreams, returning to the past, searching for traces.
العودة في الحلم إلى الماضي للبحث عن آثار باقية.
In dreams, returning to the past, searching for remaining traces.
العودة في الحلم إلى الماضي للبحث عن آثار متبقية.
In dreams, returning to the past, finding remaining traces.
العودة في الحلم إلى الماضي البارز للعثور على آثار متبقية.
(The Milky Way stretches for thousands of miles, love beyond the horizon.
(مجرة تمتد لآلاف الأميال، الحب تجاوز الأفق.
The river stretches for thousands of miles, love beyond the horizon.
النهر يمتد لآلاف الأميال، الحب تجاوز الأفق.
Protecting you, what to believe, what is love?
حمايتك، ما الذي تؤمن به، ما هو الحب.
Silently guarding, foolishly pursuing.
حماية صامتة، بحث مجنون.
I hold you, true, singing directly.
أحتضنك بصدق وأغني بصراحة.
I have you, using a true heart to sing sincerely.
أمتلكك بقلب صادق وأغني بنية مباشرة.
Not in vain to be moved, seeking to love fully.
لا داعي للتأثر عبثا، اطلب بكل قلبك.
Soon to be moved, seeking to love fully.
قريبا سيتأثر قلبي، أطلب بكل قلبي.
In vain to be moved, seeking to love fully.
التأثر عبثا، الطلب بكل القلب.